<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<EVENTLIST>
	<EVENT>	
		<ID>0</ID>
		<TITLE>Akraman</TITLE>
		<TAGLINE>The Hacking Contest</TAGLINE>
		<IMAGE>akraman.png</IMAGE>
		<DESCRIPTION>Infotsav-12 presents AKRAMAN-For all those who love to play off in the arena of hacking.
The contest would trigger off such hacking questions to vouch for the youth's knack, which will battle in the arena of simmered potential threats. Come, accept the challenge and have fun HACKING.&lt;b&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prize Money : Rs.6000&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
Visit Akraman at &lt;a href='http://ak.infotsav.org' target='_blank'&lt;b&gt;ak.infotsav.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
</DESCRIPTION>	
		<RULES>
&lt;li&gt;Team size is utmost 2 members.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The event will be held online as mentioned in the timeline.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;So, all the participants are requested to register on the Infotsav website http://www.infotsav.org for participation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The top two teams will be awarded the cash prize.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Only students who are studying in graduate and post-graduate level in any University are eligible to take part.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If any team(s) is found posting answers in any forum will be immediately disqualified without any prior notice.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Any team found having fake information regarding qualification criteria or profile information shall be immediately disqualified.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Any team which attempts to hack/deliberately crash the judging system will be immediately disqualified.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The decision of the organizers in declaring the results will be final and will be binding to all. No queries in this regard will be entertained.&lt;/li&gt;

       </RULES>
		<TIMELINE>&lt;li&gt;Online event to be held from 6th November 2012 at 08:00PM to 7th November at 11:00AM .&lt;/li&gt; 
		</TIMELINE>
		<DOWNLOADS>&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href='downloads/akraman.pdf' target='_blank'&gt;Akraman Details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;</DOWNLOADS>
		<CONTACTS>&lt;h4&gt;DSSR Akhilesh&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 7879930626&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;akhilesh@infotsav.org
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Rathnadeep Kanaparthi&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 8989131404&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;rathnadeep@infotsav.org

                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;                                                   
</CONTACTS>
		<UPDATES></UPDATES>
	</EVENT>
	<EVENT>		
		<ID>1</ID>
		<TITLE>Reverse Engineering</TITLE>
		<TAGLINE></TAGLINE>
		<IMAGE>re.png</IMAGE>
		<DESCRIPTION>Infotsav 2012 presents Reverse Engineering,a competition to prove your fundamental understanding skills as an engineer. 
		It's here to test your logical thinking along with systematic approach to analyze the pattern. You are given an executable program or 
		an application and are asked to do reverse coding, that is develop the source code.
		&lt;b&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prize Money : Rs.6000&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
		Visit Reverse Engineering at &lt;a href='http://re.infotsav.iiitm.in/' target='_blank'&lt;b&gt;http://re.infotsav.iiitm.in/&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
		</DESCRIPTION>	
		<RULES>&lt;li&gt;Candidate will participate individually.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Event will be conducted in 2 Rounds.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;First Round (Online Round) -This round will consist of 25 objective and 5 Subjective questions based on logical thinking and pattern recognition. Top 25 candidates of the first round will qualify for the final round.(Onsite) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Second Round (On-Site Round) - In this round a set of 10 executable files will be provided to you along with the valid input range for those files. After analyzing the results produced by the executable file, candidates have to write a program that will produce same results. Allowed Languages - C, C++, Java and Python..&lt;/li&gt;
</RULES>		
<TIMELINE>&lt;li&gt;First Round - 5th November 2012 (8:00 PM to 08:40PM) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Second Round - 9th Novermber 2012&lt;/li&gt;
</TIMELINE>
		<DOWNLOADS>&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href='downloads/reverse.pdf' target='_blank'&gt;Reverse Engineering Details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;</DOWNLOADS>
		<CONTACTS>&lt;h4&gt;Rajesh Kumar&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;7879741110&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail:&lt;/span&gt;rajesh.kumar@infotsav.org
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Swati Sinha&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;8989217254&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;swati.sinha@infotsav.org

                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;

													
             </CONTACTS>
		<UPDATES></UPDATES>
	</EVENT>
	<EVENT>	
		<ID>2</ID>	
		<TITLE>Code Weavers</TITLE>
		<TAGLINE>Online Programming Contest</TAGLINE>
		<IMAGE>codeweavers.png</IMAGE>
		<DESCRIPTION>Do you have the brain of a genius? The online programming contest is here for you. Show your programming skills and provide
the best possible solution you can. After all life doesn't give a second chance. So prove
yourself on the battlefield and only then you will be a great warrior.
		&lt;b&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prize Money : Rs.9000&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
		</DESCRIPTION>	
		<RULES>&lt;li&gt;Team size is at most 3 members.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This mega event will be hosted at CODECHEF (A Directi Educational Initiative). &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;So, all the participants are requested to register on the hosting website http://www.codechef.com prior to the commencement of the contest.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Only students who are studying in graduate and post-graduate level in any Indian University are eligible to take part.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Permitted languages to provide solution are C, C++ and Java.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Compilers to be used: &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;gcc (gcc (GCC) 4.1.2) for C &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;g++ (g++ (GCC) 4.1.2) for C++ &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;j2sdk1.5.0 (javac 1.5.0_10) for Java.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Submission has to be done in a proper format on the host site (via file upload/embedded frame), failing which the entries shall not be accepted.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If any team(s) is found to copy source code of other teams, that team will be immediately disqualified.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Any team found having fake information regarding qualification criteria or profile information shall be immediately disqualified.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Any team which attempts to hack/deliberately crash the judging system will be immediately disqualified.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The decision of the organizers in declaring the results will be final and will be binding to all.&lt;/li&gt;
</RULES>
		<TIMELINE>&lt;li&gt;On 7 Nov'2012&lt;/li&gt;</TIMELINE>
		<DOWNLOADS>&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href='downloads/codeweavers.pdf' target='_blank'&gt;Code Weavers Details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;</DOWNLOADS>
		<CONTACTS>&lt;h4&gt;Sachchit Bansal&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 8305532657&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;sachchit.bansal@infotsav.org
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Kumar Vimal&lt;/h4&gt;
                                  &lt;p&gt;
								  &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 9479875847&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;kumar.vimal@infotsav.org

                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Shaily Mittal&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 8817348953&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;shaily.mittal@infotsav.org
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;</CONTACTS>
		<UPDATES></UPDATES>
	</EVENT>
	<EVENT>	
		<ID>3</ID>	
		<TITLE>La Ingenious</TITLE>
		<TAGLINE>Open software contest</TAGLINE>
		<IMAGE>la.png</IMAGE>
		<DESCRIPTION>La Ingenious is the software contest under the umbrella of Infotsav 2012. It is one of the most accolades winning technical event of the festival providing a platform to judge the feasibility and usefulness of software. &lt;/br&gt;The contest will cover a vast domain of software development leaving no stone unturned.
La Ingenious will comprise of two major categories-&lt;/br&gt;
&lt;ul class='circle'&gt;
&lt;h6&gt;&lt;li&gt;Web/Desktop (Desknet)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;h6&gt;&lt;li&gt;Mobile (Andrios)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;h6&gt;	
&lt;/ul&gt;	
"A thumping amount of INR 15,000 is waiting for you. Come and grab it all."

</DESCRIPTION>	
		<RULES>&lt;h5&gt;Common Rules: &lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maximum Team size allowed: 2&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The event will take place in 2 phases. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Teams are required to register at Infotsav 2012 website.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Phase I: Send your software/app SRS and Screenshots to laingenious@infotsav.org.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SRS should not exceed 5 pages, Send 5 to 10 screenshots along with it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Phase II: Will be conducted during Infotsav with the shortlisted entries from Phase I.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The source code of the application will be taken just for judging originality and will be kept safely.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You can also participate in Andrios and Desknet simultaneously.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;None of the participants can be the part of two teams in the same domain.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;None of the teams can present more than one software in the same domain. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;Rules for Desknet:&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All technologies and platforms are allowed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We will provide computer systems for presentation but still you can bring your own laptops.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are free to build software to serve any purpose i.e. no predefined domain.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;Rules for Andrios:&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All mobile application development technologies and platforms are allowed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participants must bring their own mobile devices for presenting their applications.&lt;/li&gt;

</RULES>
		<TIMELINE>Phase 1:&lt;/br&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The participants are required to submit SRS and Screenshots of their application.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Submission Deadline: 31st October 2012&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Declaration of Shortlisted participants for Final Round: 1st November 2012&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/br&gt;
Phase 2:&lt;/br&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The participants have to present their final Software on 10th November at IIITM Gwalior.&lt;/li&gt;
</TIMELINE>
		<DOWNLOADS>&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href='downloads/La-Ingenious.pdf' target='_blank'&gt;La Ingenious Details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
		&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href='downloads/srsformat.pdf' target='_blank'&gt;SRS Format Details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;</DOWNLOADS>
		<CONTACTS>&lt;h4&gt;Joney Singhal&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;9685589253&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;joney.singhal@infotsav.org
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Surbhi Arora&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;7879918716&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;surbhi.arora@infotsav.org
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Amit Samdarshi&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;9770126368&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;amit.samdarshi@infotsav.org
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
			</CONTACTS>
		<UPDATES></UPDATES>
	</EVENT>
	<EVENT>	
		<ID>4</ID>	
		<TITLE>Web Mania</TITLE>
		<TAGLINE>Web Designing Contest</TAGLINE>
		<IMAGE>web.png</IMAGE>
		<DESCRIPTION>One of the finest way of expressing information in front of the world is
through the web. It is the designing of these web pages that would attract many people to
read the information.&lt;/br&gt;With the event web mania we bring forward a chance for you
to try your imagination and try your hands in the fascinating field of web designing. Try
to be articulate in whatever you do .Do it fast and do it perfectly. Be a professional
designer, know the psychology of color So, grab this opportunity with both your hands
and test your skills @ Web Mania.

&lt;b&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prize Money : Rs.6000&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
		</DESCRIPTION>	
		<RULES>&lt;li&gt;Team size is at most 3 members.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The event will be conducted in two phases.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Phase-1: The participants are required to mail a web-site prepared by them on the given topics only.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Phase-2: It will be an on-campus round. The best 10 teams of Phase-1 have to prepare a website on the given case provided to them during Infotsav'12.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Students pursuing graduation and post-graduation in any Indian university are eligible.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Any team found having fake information regarding qualification criteria or profile information will be immediately disqualified.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The participants are not allowed to use CMS such as Drupal or Joomla. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The contestants are requested to strictly adhere to the deadlines. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The decision of the judges and organizers will be final. No queries in this regard will be entertained.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evaluation Criteria:&lt;/li&gt;
&#160;&lt;li&gt;Design &lt;/li&gt;
&#160;&lt;li&gt;Content&lt;/li&gt;
&#160;&lt;li&gt;Innovation&lt;/li&gt;
</RULES>
		<TIMELINE>Phase - 1: 
&lt;li&gt;Start of Round 1:                          24th September 2012&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deadline for Submission:                   5th November 2012&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Declaration of Results:                    7th November 2012&lt;/li&gt;

Phase - 2: &lt;/br&gt;
Details will be uploaded soon. 
</TIMELINE>
		<DOWNLOADS>&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href='downloads/webmania.pdf' target='_blank'&gt;Web Mania Details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
		&lt;ul class='download'&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href='downloads/webmania.pdf' target='_blank'&gt;Round 1 case&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</DOWNLOADS>
		<CONTACTS>&lt;h4&gt;Ankur Mudgal&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 9617540863&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;ankur.mudgal@infotsav.org
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Nikunj Sharma&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 7879414010&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;nikunj.sharma@infotsav.org

                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Deepesh Dagar&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 7879341036&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;deepesh.dagar@infotsav.org

                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
		</CONTACTS>
		<UPDATES>To be uploaded soon</UPDATES>
	</EVENT>
	<EVENT>	
		<ID>5</ID>	
		<TITLE>Witch Hunt</TITLE>
		<TAGLINE>Debugging Contest</TAGLINE>
		<IMAGE>witch.png</IMAGE>
		<DESCRIPTION>Witch hunt, the debugging contest is not only about programming talent but also about applying the sheer knowledge to rectify errors.The challenge tests a programmer's ability to understand and respond to dissimilar codes. The art of rectification / debugging is difficult than conventional programming because it's not about what you know, it's about how much you know and how you apply those cognitive ideas to recognize errors and act upon them. The event tests the programmer in areas of speed, intellect and understanding. A programmer stands nowhere if takes ages to understand and device an algorithm, hence it requires to comply!
The ability to perceive the programming style different from one's own takes some doing and if you are up against the challenge, better get started by becoming a part of Witch Hunt.
&lt;b&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prize Money : Rs.6000&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
Visit Witch Hunt at &lt;a href='http://witchhunt.infotsav.org' target='_blank'&lt;b&gt;witchhunt.infotsav.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
</DESCRIPTION>	
		<RULES>&lt;li&gt;Maximum Team size is 2.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; No late submissions will be entertained. (unless the time limit is extended).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You aren't allowed to skip a question and return to it later.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Event is divided in two Phases&lt;/li&gt;
     &lt;li&gt; Phase I - Preliminary Phase (Online)&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Phase II - Main Phase ( At ABV-IIITM, Gwalior Campus) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;First Phase will consist of three levels:&lt;/li&gt;
&#160;&lt;li&gt;First level will consist of multiple choice questions (only one correct) with negative (-) marking. &lt;/li&gt;
&#160;&lt;li&gt;Second level will consist of multiple choice questions (one or more than one correct) with no negative (-) marking.&lt;/li&gt;
&#160;&lt;li&gt;Third level will consist of submit type questions with no negative (-) marking. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Number of questions and duration will be disclosed at the time of contest.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Any team which attempts to hack/deliberately crash the judging system will be immediately disqualified. &lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;The decision of the organizers in declaring the results will be final. No queries in this regard will be entertained.&lt;/li&gt;
</RULES>
		<TIMELINE>&lt;li&gt;Preliminary Round for IIITM Students: 5th Nov'12 (5:00 PM to 7:00 PM) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Preliminary Round for Outsiders will be held during Infotsav&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Result Declaration:	7th Nov'12&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Main Round:		10th Nov'12&lt;/li&gt;
</TIMELINE>
		<DOWNLOADS>&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href='downloads/witchhunt.pdf' target='_blank'&gt;Witch Hunt Details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;</DOWNLOADS>
		<CONTACTS>&lt;h4&gt;Pranshu Agrawal&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 9479810518&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;pranshu.agrawal@infotsav.org

                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Vikas Mittal&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 9669839980&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt; vikas.mittal@infotsav.org

                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Archie Jain&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 7879337979&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;archie.jain@infotsav.org

                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                     &lt;/br&gt;
</CONTACTS>
		<UPDATES>To be uploaded soon</UPDATES>
	</EVENT>
	<EVENT>	
		<ID>6</ID>	
		<TITLE>Analyst</TITLE>
		<TAGLINE>Case Study Competition</TAGLINE>
		<IMAGE>analyst.png</IMAGE>
		<DESCRIPTION>Analyst-The Case Study Event is all about
judging your intellect, managerial skills and ability to craft sustainable solutions to
problems that organizations face today. If you can strain you nerve and sinew, and come
up with solutions that are practical and implementable, Analyst has a place for you.
Challenging live cases from some great ventures await your sight, who knows... may be
you can make a difference! Analyst this year comes with interesting cases, mindboggling
reasoning and some big people to judge your acumen and innovation. &lt;ul class='download'&gt;
&lt;b&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prize Money : Rs.12,000&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;b&gt;&lt;li&gt;Results of Round 1 are out. Check you email for results. Results are also available on &lt;u&gt; 
&lt;a href='https://www.facebook.com/analyst2012' target='_blank'&gt;Facebook Page&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/u&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
</DESCRIPTION>	
		<RULES>&lt;li&gt;Team size: 4 members&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The winners will be announced on the basis of presentation and the final document submitted.&lt;/li&gt;
</RULES>
		<TIMELINE>&lt;h6&gt;Preliminary Phase:&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Case to be uploaded on : 25thSeptember,2012&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deadline for submission : 15th October,2012&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Results of Preliminary Phase : 20th October2012&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;h6&gt;Final Phase:&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Presentation on-campus : 9thNovember,2012&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enclosure of Live-case : After completion of Presentation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dead-line for submission : 11th November,2012&lt;/li&gt;
</TIMELINE>
		<DOWNLOADS>&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href='downloads/analyst.pdf' target='_blank'&gt;Analyst Details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
		&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href='downloads/Analyst_Case.pdf' target='_blank'&gt;Analyst Case for Phase 1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;</DOWNLOADS>
		<CONTACTS>&lt;h4&gt;Dheeraj Purohit &lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 8989283394&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;dheerajkumar.purohit@infotsav.org
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Maryam Dairkee &lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 9425756433&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;maryam.dairkee@infotsav.org
                                                 &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
													
             
			 &lt;h4&gt;Mohini Gupta  &lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 9926330688&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;mohini.gupta@infotsav.org


                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;</CONTACTS>
		<UPDATES>To be uploaded soon</UPDATES>
	</EVENT>
	<EVENT>	
		<ID>7</ID>	
		<TITLE>Brouhaha</TITLE>
		<TAGLINE>Advertising Competition</TAGLINE>
		<IMAGE>brouhaha.png</IMAGE>
		<DESCRIPTION>
		
		&lt;p&gt;Brouhaha is the advertising contest that is
held under Infotsav. Advertising is a form of communication that
typically attempts to persuade potential customers to purchase or to consume more of a
particular brand of product or service. Advertisements are designed to generate increased
consumption of those products and services through the creation and reinforcement of
"brand image" and "brand loyalty". Every major medium is used to deliver these
messages, including television, radio, cinema, magazines, newspapers, video games, the
Internet and billboards.
&lt;ul class='download'&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href='downloads/brouhaha_case.pdf' target='_blank'&gt;Round 1 case&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;b&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prize Money : Rs.12,000&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/b&gt;


</DESCRIPTION>	

		<RULES>&lt;li&gt;The maximum size of a team is three.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The logos provided are to be used in every advertisement. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Two print advertisements, one audio advertisement and one video advertisement(optional) should be submitted. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;While preparing the advertisement the use of the name of rival companies is prohibited.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The print advertisements should be targeting newspapers and magazines. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The video advertisement should not be more than 40 seconds and should be in .mpg, .avi or .flv format and flash presentation is also allowed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The audio advertisement should not be more than 20 seconds long and should be in .mp3 or .wmv format.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advertisements will be judged on the basis of their originality, design and tagline/caption used.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Legality of the advertisements is foremost priority.  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Presentation should be in ENGLISH only. The language HINDI is also allowed but can be used only in video and audio advertisement.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The participants are required to send the soft copy of their entry to the mail id brouhaha@infotsav.org. A document providing the name of the team, members of the team, name of the institute, e-mail addresses and contact numbers is to be submitted along with the advertisements.&lt;/li&gt;
</RULES>
		<TIMELINE>
&lt;b&gt;Phase 1(online phase)&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Case to be uploaded on : 6th October,2012&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deadline for submission : 25th October,2012&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Results of Preliminary Phase : 29th October2012&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Phase 2 (On-campus)&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The participants shortlisted have to present their first phase product advertisement describing
them in detail.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Phase 3(On-campus)&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The product for the third phase will be uploaded, after short listing the participants for second
phase.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The participants shortlisted for the second phase continue to the third phase and are to
present advertisements of next product describing them in detail.&lt;/li&gt;
		
		</TIMELINE>
		<DOWNLOADS>&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href='downloads/brouhaha.pdf' target='_blank'&gt;Brouhaha Details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
		&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href='downloads/brouhaha_case.pdf' target='_blank'&gt;Round 1 case &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
		&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href='downloads/brouhaha_timeline.pdf' target='_blank'&gt;Timeline&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
		</DOWNLOADS>
		<CONTACTS>&lt;h4&gt;Mukul Kumar&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 9098530117&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;mukul.kumar@infotsav.org
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                  
&lt;h4&gt;Divya Jain&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 7828309266&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;divya.jain@infotsav.org
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    
													
             &lt;h4&gt;Kajol Nigam&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 8989417346&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;kajol.nigam@infotsav.org
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    
&lt;h4&gt;Shubham Singh&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 9009329575&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;shubham.singh@infotsav.org
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
													
             </CONTACTS>
		<UPDATES>To be uploaded soon</UPDATES>
	</EVENT>
	<EVENT>	
		<ID>8</ID>	
		<TITLE>Pinnacle</TITLE>
		<TAGLINE>B-Plan Contest</TAGLINE>
		<IMAGE>pinnacle.png</IMAGE>
		<DESCRIPTION>If you have a unique idea that carves you out as a successful entrepreneur, then we
welcome you to the most appreciated event of Infotsav. It provides your idea, a platform
and eventually a spark just sufficient to ignite you. So what are you waiting for? It's show
time.
Pinnacle is the flagship event of Infotsav'12 which is being conducted from 09th to 11th
November 2012. The event is attracting students from the best B-schools and Engineering
colleges around the country. &lt;b&gt;&lt;/br&gt;Prize Money
&lt;li&gt;First Prize : Rs.15000&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Second Prize: Rs.10000&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
The winning Business Plan will be mentored by Incubation Centre ABV-IIITM.&lt;/b&gt;
</DESCRIPTION>	
		<RULES>&lt;li&gt;There is no registration fee.&lt;/li&gt; 
&lt;li&gt;Executive Summary and all other documents/queries to be sent to pinnacle@infotsav.org &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A team should comprise of a maximum of 4 members. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strictly adhere to the format mentioned. To view the format go to download section. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Business plans on company/start up registered before 1st September, 2011 are not eligible to participate. Entries must contain the original work of participants. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The decision of the judges and organizers will be final and binding to all the participants. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Any of the terms and conditions can be changed by the organizers anytime ensuring to give the participants appropriate time to respond to the changes. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;The B-plans will be evaluated based on following criteria's:-&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The clarity and potential of the market opportunity. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Innovativeness of business concept. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Feasibility of the plan. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The overall evaluation of potential reward to risk. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Marketing Strategy. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Financial Analysis. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sustainability and Scalability of Business Model. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Quality of presentation.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
</RULES>
		<TIMELINE>
&lt;li&gt;1st phase: Executive summary Submission: 18th September - 15th October: Results on 18th October.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2nd phase: Final presentation at the campus.&lt;/li&gt;
</TIMELINE>
		<DOWNLOADS>&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href='downloads/pinnacle.pdf' target='_blank'&gt;Pinnacle Details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;</DOWNLOADS>
		<CONTACTS>&lt;h4&gt;Pankhuri Agarwal&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone:&lt;/span&gt;8989217242&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;pankhuri.agarwal@infotsav.org
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Shranith Linga&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone:&lt;/span&gt;8817051093
&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;shranith.linga@infotsav.org
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Ankit Shukla&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;8815223733
&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail:&lt;/span&gt;ankit.shukla@infotsav.org
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
												</CONTACTS>
		<UPDATES>To be uploaded soon</UPDATES>
	</EVENT>
	<EVENT>
		<ID>9</ID>	
		<TITLE>Tycoon</TITLE>
		<TAGLINE>Best manager contest</TAGLINE>
		<IMAGE>tycoon.png</IMAGE>
		<DESCRIPTION>Are you outstanding from the crowd? But we
need here someone who can lead them. Competing increases you incrementally but
Co-operating does it exponentially. The stage is set for you. "Come, participate with
hundreds to stand against millions".Tycoon is the Best manager contest of Infotsav.
It is a quest to determine the person who is most knowledgeable of the who's who of the
business fraternity. The contest is an individual one to make the competition more cut
throat and fierce. Add to it the elimination at each level, thus making the competition all
the more ruthless. But ultimately who so ever comes out as the winner gets to taste the
forbidden fruit. He/She is accorded the title of the tycoon.
&lt;b&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prize Money : Rs.8000&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
</DESCRIPTION>	
		<RULES>&lt;li&gt;Round 1: Online quiz containing small puzzles and brief descriptive questions. Those qualified shall proceed to round 2.
  OR
Offline quiz for internal and on the spot participants.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Round 2:
Group discussion: Shortlisted candidates participate in GD round and selected candidates proceed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Round 3:
Short b-plan contest: Each finalist gets to present a b-plan in stipulated in time. &lt;/li&gt;
</RULES>
		<TIMELINE>&lt;li&gt;Round 1:- Online round : &lt;a href='http://goo.gl/37Sk6' target='_blank'> &lt;b&gt;click here&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; to begin  &lt;/li&gt;
                   &lt;li&gt;Top 30 participants of Round 1 will proceed to Round 2 and Top 3 entries will get "EXCLUSIVE GIFT HAMPERS"&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deadline:- 28th october 2012&lt;/li&gt;
</TIMELINE>
		<DOWNLOADS></DOWNLOADS>
		<CONTACTS>&lt;h4&gt;Naivedya Jain&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone:&lt;/span&gt;7509926326
&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;naivedya.jain@infotsav.org
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;P. Swaroop Singh &lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone:&lt;/span&gt;8103911113
&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;p.swaroop@infotsav.org
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Devanshi Gupta&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;9009686622
&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail:&lt;/span&gt;devanshi.gupta@infotsav.org
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;</CONTACTS>
		<UPDATES>To be uploaded soon</UPDATES>
	</EVENT>
	<EVENT>	
		<ID>10</ID>	
		<TITLE>Forex</TITLE>
		<TAGLINE>Foreign Exchange Market</TAGLINE>
		<IMAGE>forex.png</IMAGE>
		<DESCRIPTION>Forex is the simulation of by far the largest financial market in the world that includes trading between central banks, currency speculators, 
		multinational corporations, governments and other financial institutions. This game provides a platform where the players can convert virtual money from one 
		currency to another. The player who has the maximum assets wins. The Foreign Exchange market exists whenever one currency is traded for another. 
		It gives a real time experience of the "foreign exchange" provided with virtual money and real time data to get the invaluable hand on experience.
&lt;b&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prize Money : Rs.6000&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/b&gt;

 Play Forex at &lt;a href='http://forex.infotsav.org/' target='_blank'&lt;b&gt;http://forex.infotsav.org/&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
		</DESCRIPTION>	
		<RULES>&lt;li&gt;Only registered users at http://www.infotsav.org/ can participate.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A participant can make his/her another account only if his earlier account is freezed. In case it is found that the participant has created more than one user id he/she shall be disqualified. In case of any discrepancy organizers decisions will be final.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;There is only one round.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In this round the participants have to trade with the virtual amount of $ one lakh. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In case of tie, the organizer's decision will be final.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rank will be calculated after every hour.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The top ten players (as according to the rank) will be scrutinized for any fraud or fake transactions. The Final Winners shall be then intimated through mail and a list will be put up on the website.&lt;/li&gt;
</RULES>
		<TIMELINE>&lt;li&gt;From 2nd November 2012 (9:00:00) to 8 Nov' 2012 (23:59:59)&lt;/li&gt;</TIMELINE>
		<DOWNLOADS>&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href='downloads/forex
		.pdf' target='_blank'&gt;Forex Details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;</DOWNLOADS>
		<CONTACTS>&lt;h4&gt;Prashant Gupta&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 9770272350&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;prashant.gupta@infotsav.org
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
													&lt;h4&gt;Saurabh Maurya&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 8989923577&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;saurabh.maurya@infotsav.org
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;</CONTACTS>
		<UPDATES>To be uploaded soon</UPDATES>
	</EVENT>
	<EVENT>	
		<ID>11</ID>	
		<TITLE>Stock Sutra</TITLE>
		<TAGLINE>Enquity Research Contest</TAGLINE>
		<IMAGE>stock.png</IMAGE>
		<DESCRIPTION>The game is a test of analyzing and
diagnosing powers of participants as some shares tumble and some soar at the stock
market during the contest period. The participants are free to trade during market open
and close hours. An event in which the investment acumen of the contestants is tested where the
contestants have to invest in stocks and have to explain their investment strategy. In the
present accelerating growth period of the Indian economy, banks and other financial
institutions are in acute need of good analytical minds for their investment decisions.
&lt;b&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prize Money : Rs.6000&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/b&gt;

 Play Stock Sutra at &lt;a href='http://stock.infotsav.org/' target='_blank'&lt;b&gt;http://stock.infotsav.org/&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
</DESCRIPTION>	
		<RULES>&lt;li&gt;Event will be played online for about 2 weeks.
&lt;li&gt;The   participants   registering   are  provided   an  initial amount of Rs1,00,000  and  required  to  trade  in  stocks  from  the  NIFTY  index  and NIFTY&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;JUNIOR index:- The game is a test of analyzing and diagnosing powers of participants as  some   shares  tumble   and   some   soar  at the  stock  market during&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Contest period:- The  participants  are free to  trade  during market  open  and  close  hours.  At  the  end  of  the  contest,the  participant  with highest  net worth is thewinner.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The decision of Judges and organizing team would be final and binding.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The    Players  should   strictly  adhere   to deadlines   mentioned     in the  brochure. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Players   are  requested    to  avail  accommodation      by  contacting   the hospitality team of Infotsav, 2012.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Any     immediate     changes    in   the   deadlines    due   to   unforeseen circumstances would be communicated through our website-www.infotsav.org&lt;/li&gt;
</RULES>
		<TIMELINE>&lt;li&gt;From 1st Nov 2012 -  7 Nov 2012 (Daily 9:15 AM to 3:55 PM)&lt;/li&gt;</TIMELINE>
		<DOWNLOADS>&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href='downloads/stocksutra.pdf' target='_blank'&gt;Stock Sutra Details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;</DOWNLOADS>
		<CONTACTS>&lt;h4&gt;Siddharth Bhatia&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 7898042636&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;siddharth.bhatia@infotsav.org
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
													&lt;h4&gt;Neetesh Kumar&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 7898281444&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;neetesh.kumar@infotsav.org
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;</CONTACTS>
		<UPDATES>To be uploaded soon</UPDATES>
	</EVENT>
	<EVENT>	
		<ID>12</ID>	
		<TITLE>Trove Trace</TITLE>
		<TAGLINE>Online Treasure Hunt</TAGLINE>
		<IMAGE>trove.png</IMAGE>
		<DESCRIPTION>Does searching for a hidden treasure
fascinate you? Are you enthralled by clues and puzzles and want to step into the shoes of
the master detective Holmes?? Then look no further, Trove Trace is where you should be.
There is nothing like a good riddle or a clue to spice up your hunt.
All the techno-freaks and pirates of the virtual world out there, trove trace is back - with
murkier corners, crazier questions, more twists and turns to blow your brains out, and a
monstrous amount of fun.
&lt;b&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prize Money : Rs.6000&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/b&gt;

 Play Trove Trace at &lt;a href='http://tt.infotav.org/' target='_blank'&lt;b&gt;http://tt.infotav.org/&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
</DESCRIPTION>	
		<RULES>
&lt;li&gt;The event will be held online as mentioned in the timeline.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;So,all the participants are requested to register on the Infotsav website http://www.infotsav.org for participation. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The top two participants will be awarded the cash prize.&lt;/li&gt; 
&lt;li&gt;Only students who are studying in graduate and post-graduate level in any Indian University are eligible to take part.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If anyone is found posting answers in any form will be immediately disqualified without any prior notice. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Anyone found having fake information regarding qualification criteria or profile information shall be immediately disqualified.&lt;/li&gt; 
&lt;li&gt;Anyone which attempts to hack/deliberately crash the judging system will be immediately disqualified.&lt;/li&gt; 
&lt;li&gt;The decision of the organizers in declaring the results will be final and will be binding to all. No queries in this regard will be entertained.&lt;/li&gt;</RULES>
		<TIMELINE>&lt;li&gt;On 7th Nov 2012 (5:00 PM to 07:59 PM)&lt;/li&gt;
		</TIMELINE>
		<DOWNLOADS>&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href='downloads/trovetrace.pdf' target='_blank'&gt;Trove Trace Details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;</DOWNLOADS>
		<CONTACTS>&lt;h4&gt;K. E. Pradeep&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone:&lt;/span&gt;8989924738
&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;pradeep.ke@infotsav.org

                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Nidhi Gupta&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone:&lt;/span&gt;8817407802
&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;nidhi.gupta@infotsav.org
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Gopu Hemalatha&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;8989134551
&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail:&lt;/span&gt;hemalatha.gopu@infotsav.org
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;</CONTACTS>
		<UPDATES>To be uploaded soon</UPDATES>
	</EVENT>
	<EVENT>	
		<ID>13</ID>	
		<TITLE>Job Bureau</TITLE>
		<TAGLINE>Virtual Job</TAGLINE>
		<IMAGE>job.png</IMAGE>
		<DESCRIPTION>Get to use the world's latest technologies and software.
It's time for you to experience the professional serene and achieve what you desire and are really capable of.
Infotsav gives you a chance to get placed before the actual campus drive in a virtual world where you learn to be an efficient project leader and a skilled coder. The simulation takes you into the flock of assignments where you move ahead by gaining experience and money. The game checks your skills at choosing the right project at the right time, a single wrong move could forestall your winning chances.
&lt;b&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prize Money : Rs.6000&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
 Play Job Bureau at &lt;a href='http://job.infotsav.org/' target='_blank'&lt;b&gt;http://job.infotsav.org/&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
</DESCRIPTION>	
		<RULES>&lt;li&gt;Only registered users at http://www.infotsav.org/ can participate.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;As soon as you register, you become a freelancer/software engineer/project leader who gets paid for completing tasks of various companies. The user is virtually provided with a laptop of basic configuration with fully charged battery.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The criteria for completing a task include your battery level and fulfilment of minimum requirements by a task which may include various software and hardware.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The tasks are categorized into four levels.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;User will get paid for completing a task and gains experience associated with that task.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The battery gets consumed in doing a task/job. If battery gets over, one needs to wait for some time to recharge the battery or buy a power booster for the laptop for instant recharge.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;User can upgrade his/her system by buying available packages (hardware and software).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The basis of ranking is the "experience" gained by the user.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;There are three basic tasks kept for the user in case if he runs out of money. These tasks will not give him experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;There is only one round.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Under any malicious practice found, the organizers decision will be bound and final.&lt;/li&gt;
</RULES>
		<TIMELINE>&lt;li&gt;From 2 Nov' 2012(12:00 PM) to 4 Nov' 2012(11:59 PM)&lt;/li&gt;</TIMELINE>
		<DOWNLOADS>&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href='downloads/jobbureau.pdf' target='_blank'&gt;Job Bureau Details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;</DOWNLOADS>
		<CONTACTS>&lt;h4&gt;Akashdeep Saluja&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 8989931179&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;akashdeep.saluja@infotsav.org

                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
													&lt;h4&gt;Priyam Bajaj&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 8827448056&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;priyam.bajaj@infotsav.org

                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;</CONTACTS>
		<UPDATES>To be uploaded soon</UPDATES>
	</EVENT>
	<EVENT>	
		<ID>14</ID>	
		<TITLE>Dus Ka Dum</TITLE>
		<TAGLINE></TAGLINE>
		<IMAGE></IMAGE>
		<DESCRIPTION></DESCRIPTION>	
		<RULES>To be uploaded soon</RULES>
		<TIMELINE>To be uploaded soon</TIMELINE>
		<DOWNLOADS></DOWNLOADS>
		<CONTACTS>To be uploaded soon</CONTACTS>
		<UPDATES>To be uploaded soon</UPDATES>
	</EVENT>
	<EVENT>	
		<ID>15</ID>	
		<TITLE>Enigma</TITLE>
		<TAGLINE>IT Quiz</TAGLINE>
		<IMAGE>enigma.png</IMAGE>
		<DESCRIPTION>A quiz is usually a form of a student assessment, but  has fewer questions of lesser difficulty and requires less time for completion than a test. It is to celebrate this spirit that Infotsav conducts Enigma.
Enigma will have a preliminary round of offline quiz and only the top scoring teams will compete in the mains against each other. So brace yourself to be a part of techno- managerial quiz to compete with the best brains of the youth. This is the war of grey cells. So let us watch who meets the target superbly! We need your cooperation to move ahead in taking it to another level and achieve unfathomable level of excellence and popularity.
&lt;b&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prize Money : Rs.6000&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/b&gt;

Visit Enigma at &lt;a href='http://enigma.infotsav.org' target='_blank'&lt;b&gt;enigma.infotsav.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
</DESCRIPTION>	
		<RULES>&lt;li&gt;The quiz will comprise of 2 levels - Prelims and Mains&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All participants must be bonafide students of an educational institution.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The top scoring teams will qualify for the mains to compete against each other.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The participating teams should be comprised of at most 3 members per team.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The scoring pattern, number of questions etc. shall depend on the quiz master.&lt;/li&gt;
</RULES>
		<TIMELINE>Prelims :
&lt;li&gt;For IIITM Students: 4th Nov 2012 (5:30 PM to 7:30 PM).&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/br&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For Non-IIITM Students: will be held on 9th November 2012.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/br&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mains will be held at ABV-IIITM Campus.&lt;/li&gt;</TIMELINE>
		<DOWNLOADS>&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href='downloads/enigma.pdf' target='_blank'&gt;Enigma Details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;</DOWNLOADS>
		<CONTACTS>&lt;h4&gt;Vinayak Meena&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 7879650966&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;vinayak.meena@infotsav.org

                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Itisha Jain&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 7879749369&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;itisha.jain@infotsav.org

                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Divesh Burnwal&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 7879009450&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt; divesh.burnwal@infotsav.org
	
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
		</CONTACTS>
		<UPDATES>To be uploaded soon</UPDATES>
	</EVENT><EVENT>	
		<ID>16</ID>	
		<TITLE>Chakravyuh</TITLE>
		<TAGLINE>BITQUIZ</TAGLINE>
		<IMAGE>chakra.png</IMAGE>
		<DESCRIPTION>Chakravyuh - The BITquiz , where the best brains try to outsmart each other with their power of knowledge. Show the world that you know about what's happening in it and you are not just a book worm. With CHAKRAVYUH, we plan to provide a platform to all the quizzing minds and intellects across the country to showcase their innovative ideas, thoughts, experience, logic and skills in a battle of wits to finally succeed and be hailed as winner. 
		While the battle ground of CHAKRAVYUH is being built, sharpen your mind to storm with the sharper minds with a passion for the techno-managerial world. Put on your skill-suit, Get yourself ready, The Game is about to begin...
&lt;b&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prize Money : Rs.6000&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
Visit Chakravyuh at &lt;a href='http://chakra.infotsav.org' target='_blank'&lt;b&gt;chakra.infotsav.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
</DESCRIPTION>	
		<RULES>&lt;li&gt;Event is divided into Three phases:&lt;/li&gt;
Preliminary phase&lt;/br&gt;
Secondary phase&lt;/br&gt;
Final phase&lt;/br&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Preliminary phase will be conducted online. This Phase will consist of multiple choice questions (only one correct) with negative (-) marking.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Secondary phase consists of QUIZ round. It will be conducted offline at ABV-IIITM campus. Participants will be required to make a team of three members among themselves in this phase.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Final phase consists of two parts:&lt;/li&gt;
Just a minute (JAM).&lt;/br&gt;
Group discussion (GD).
&lt;li&gt;The decision of the organizers in declaring the results will be final. No queries in this regard will be entertained.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You aren't allowed to back and re-submit any question in the Online phase.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Any user who attempts to hack/deliberately crash the judging system will be immediately disqualified.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Number of questions &amp; duration will be disclosed at the time game starts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Only submissions which reach us within the time limit will be evaluated (unless the duration is extended).&lt;/li&gt;
</RULES>
		<TIMELINE>&lt;li&gt;Preliminary Phase will be conducted online on 6th Nov'2012 from 6:00 PM to 7:30 PM for IIITM students.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Secondary Phase will be conducted On-campus on 9th Nov' 2012.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Final Phase will be conducted On-campus on 10th Nov' 2012.&lt;/li&gt;
</TIMELINE>
		<DOWNLOADS>&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href='downloads/chakravyuh.pdf' target='_blank'&gt;Chakravyuh Details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;</DOWNLOADS>
		<CONTACTS>&lt;h4&gt;Annupriya&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;7879749375&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;annu.priya@infotsav.org

                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Sai Kumar&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;9479829998&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;saikumar.chelkapally@infotsav.org

                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Prashant Gupta&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;8889710670&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;prashant@infotsav.org
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;</CONTACTS>
		<UPDATES>To be uploaded soon</UPDATES>
	</EVENT>
	<EVENT>	
				<ID>17</ID>	
		<TITLE>Sameeksha</TITLE>
		<TAGLINE>Paper Presentation Contest</TAGLINE>
		<IMAGE>sameeksha.png</IMAGE>
		<DESCRIPTION>The toughest job for mankind is to do any job the easiest way and since ages man has been effortlessly trying to do the same. Techno-management is the theme of Sameeksha-the Annual National Paper Presentation Contest that stages brilliant ideas and innovations in the field of technology and management and allows young researchers and students both at UG/PG level to bring forth the novel ideas that they have worked upon.
Sameeksha has been giving great opportunities for
exploring new dimensions of knowledge, understanding the needs and identifying the best perspectives for the future. In our constant endeavor to make Sameeksha a cut above the rest and different from the league of similar competitions, we ensure that the papers get evaluated by the most renowned and eminent scholars and well-known figures from the business industry to magnify even the microscopic errors that may be far out of sight of the presenters and ensure true evaluation of the papers.
Sameeksha beckons the driving force of the future. Sameeksha beckons YOU!.
&lt;b&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prize Money : Rs.12,000&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		</DESCRIPTION>	
		<RULES>&lt;li&gt;Participants can be UG/PG/Research Scholars.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A team consists of maximum four members and an individual can be a part of just one team, however there can be any number of entries from a T-school or a B-school.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The paper should not exceed 15 pages or 3000 words, whichever is lesser
(including everything except the annexure).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The soft copies of papers must be typed in Microsoft Office with font Times New Roman, font size 12 and a line spacing of 1.5 strictly. Headings and sub-headings can be Bold and font size needs to be 14 and
12 respectively.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The papers must follow Harvard style of referencing and standard IEEE format.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The papers should be original in their content and not published
anywhere else.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Each entry should have a cover page mentioning names of the author(s), field chosen and the topic of the paper, addresses, and e-mail and telephone numbers. This cover page shall be detached before the papers are given for panel evaluation. The name(s) of the author(s) or their institute should not appear anywhere in the body of the paper.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The file should be strictly in .pdf format.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The participants are required to send the soft copy of their entry to the
mail id sameeksha@infotsav.org.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The acknowledgment for the receipt of papers shall be sent within 24 hours of submission.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The team should bring their paper in hard copy (3 in number).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The decisions of the organizers of Sameeksha and the Panel of Judges shall be final and will be binding on all the participants.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Failure to comply with any of the rules above will lead to disqualification.&lt;/li&gt;</RULES>
		<TIMELINE>&lt;h6&gt;Online Submission of papers&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;li&gt;25th October, 2012 11:59 pm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h6&gt;On campus presentation&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;li&gt;9th November, 2012 3:00PM onwards&lt;/li&gt;</TIMELINE>
		<DOWNLOADS>&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href='downloads/sameeksha.pdf' target='_blank'&gt;Sameeksha Details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;</DOWNLOADS>
		<CONTACTS>&lt;h4&gt;Sandesh Kumar&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 7879338680&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;sandesh.kumar@infotsav.org
	
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Nitish Sharma&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 8989931104&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;nitish.sharma@infotsav.org

                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
													
             
			 &lt;h4&gt;Ritika Kurele&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 9977083908&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;ritika.kurele@infotsav.org

                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;</CONTACTS>
		<UPDATES>To be uploaded soon</UPDATES>
	</EVENT>
	<EVENT>	
		<ID>18</ID>	
		<TITLE>Gamiacs</TITLE>
		<TAGLINE></TAGLINE>
		<IMAGE>gamiacs.png</IMAGE>
		<DESCRIPTION>The battle of the virtual world has
		begun. Are you game? This Infotsav 12 the world will be rocked by the cyber warriors.
		Gamiacs is back with a bang. And this time it's not only more competitive and tougher
		but it has added an all new dimension in its already humungous artillery of
		entertainment.This time round different games will be organized to bring out the
		ultimate gamer who resides somewhere in you! So gear up, reload thy guns, sharpen you
		knifes and prepare for the ultimate burnout. Counter-Strike is about as close as you'll ever get to saving the world; or destroying it!
		Now Counter-Strike will never be the same!
		</DESCRIPTION>	
		<RULES>To be uploaded soon</RULES>
		<TIMELINE>To be uploaded soon</TIMELINE>
		<DOWNLOADS></DOWNLOADS>
		<CONTACTS>&lt;h4&gt;Akash Garg&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 7828733100&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;akash.garg@infotsav.org
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Ashu Soran&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 8964969799&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;ashu.soran@infotsav.org
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
													
             
			 &lt;h4&gt;Ichchit Agrawal&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 9425777668&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;ichchit.agrawal@infotsav.org
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;</CONTACTS>
		<UPDATES>To be uploaded soon</UPDATES>
	</EVENT>
	<EVENT>
			<ID>19</ID>	
		<TITLE>Nutshell</TITLE>
		<TAGLINE>The Linux Quiz</TAGLINE>
		<IMAGE>nutshell.png</IMAGE>
		<DESCRIPTION>Linux is the most popular open source Operating System in the world. Because of its flexibility and awesomeness, it has been widely accepted for the use of power devices, ranging from Smart phones to servers, from Kindle to the Large Hydron Collider. 
We are here to test how many students do know about Linux, which has recently emerged as a trend among the tech-freaks.
So, get ready guys because this game is going to be fun and thrilling. You'll get what you'll expect the least. 
&lt;b&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prize Money : Rs.6000&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
		</DESCRIPTION>	
		<RULES>&lt;li&gt;A team of two participants has to be formed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participants found using any inappropriate means to get the answer will be straightaway disqualified.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hail Linux Round: 1st Round - MCQ on Linux. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Linux Tic Tac Toe: 2nd Round - A linux tic tac toe to be completed by the teams.&lt;/li&gt;
</RULES>
		<TIMELINE>To be uploaded soon</TIMELINE>
		<DOWNLOADS></DOWNLOADS>
		<CONTACTS>&lt;h4&gt;Manuj Tewari &lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 9425742031&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;manuj.tewari@infotsav.org
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Ashaya Shukla &lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 9201055451&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;ashaya.shukla@infotsav.org
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
                                                    </CONTACTS>
		<UPDATES>To be uploaded soon</UPDATES>
		</EVENT>
<EVENT>	
		<ID>20</ID>	
		<TITLE>synC</TITLE>
		<TAGLINE>C/C++ Quiz</TAGLINE>
		<IMAGE>sync.png</IMAGE>
		<DESCRIPTION>A quiz is a qualitative as well as a quantitative juncture of accessing your know-how. This is a fantastic mixture of the level of quality and knowledge, which along with checking your knowledge also tests your skills acquired. As far as it is concerned of  C and C++,on one side, where C is an imperative (procedural) language and like most imperative languages in the ALGOL tradition, C has facilities for structured programming and allows lexical variable scope and recursion, whereas on the other hand C++ is a statically typed, free-form, multi-paradigm, compiled, general-purpose programming language and is one of the most popular programming languages which is implemented on a wide variety of hardware and operating system platforms. For the same cause and with the same enthusiasm, we are here on the platform of Infotsav. Get yourself boost up, with the basics as well as the hidden lethal concepts of computer programming. And we guarantee, you are surely going to witness a new phase of concepts.
		&lt;b&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prize Money : Rs.6000&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
		</DESCRIPTION>	
		<RULES>&lt;li&gt;There will be two rounds, namely 'Dennis Ritchie' Round for the 1st and 'Bjarne Stroustrup' Round for the 2nd.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The participating teams must comprise of at most 3 members in each team.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Each member of the team must be regular bonafide student of any Institute. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The teams scoring maximum in the first round will qualify for the second and the final round.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In any case, the whole rights are concerned with the organisers.&lt;/li&gt;
</RULES>
		<TIMELINE>&lt;li&gt;For all the teams, the quiz will be held on the 10th November 2012.&lt;/li&gt;</TIMELINE>
		<DOWNLOADS>&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href='downloads/synC.pdf' target='_blank'&gt;SynC Details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;</DOWNLOADS>
		<CONTACTS>&lt;h4&gt;Upendra kumar &lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 9165071692&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt; upendra.kumar@infotsav.org
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Partho Pratim Mandal &lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 7879918878&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;parthopratim.mandal@infotsav.org
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
</CONTACTS>
		<UPDATES>To be uploaded soon</UPDATES>
	</EVENT>		
	
	<EVENT>	
		<ID>21</ID>	
		<TITLE>Class-Byte</TITLE>
		<TAGLINE></TAGLINE>
		<IMAGE>Class-Byte.png</IMAGE>
		<DESCRIPTION>Class-Byte is a JAVA Quiz. Java is definitely the most popular programming language. Its features made it different from other languages like platform independence.
A breakneck questionnaire that will discover adroit  JAVA programmers. 
Round 1: Quiz on paper.
Round 2: Rapid Fire Round.
&lt;b&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prize Money : Rs.6000&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
		</DESCRIPTION>	
		<RULES>&lt;li&gt;The following is the schedule for Class-Byte!!!!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Round 1(On Paper Quiz)&lt;/b&gt;
A Paper-Quiz will be conducted. 5 teams will be selected for the  next Round.&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Round 2&lt;/b&gt;
In Rapid fire round,back to back short questions will be asked to each team. 3 Teams will be selected for the final round.&lt;/li&gt;

</RULES>
		<TIMELINE>To be uploaded soon</TIMELINE>
		<DOWNLOADS></DOWNLOADS>
		<CONTACTS>&lt;h4&gt;Vishwas Gupta &lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 9479876386&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;vishwas.gupta@infotsav.org
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Rajesh Raushan &lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 8989923544&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;rajesh.roushan@infotsav.org
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
</CONTACTS>
		<UPDATES>To be uploaded soon</UPDATES>
	</EVENT>
	
	<EVENT>	
		<ID>22</ID>	
		<TITLE>Line Sequentes</TITLE>
		<TAGLINE></TAGLINE>
		<IMAGE>Line-Sequentes.png</IMAGE>
		<DESCRIPTION>The line sequentes will basically be an event for the beginners in which they will have to compete with their line following robots 
		in the given arena and beat their respective opponents in terms of speed and time limits. This basic robot has to follow the black line on the background, taking the right turns. 
		The follower has to complete the race without losing the line. Each team gets one chance, and the team which finishes the race accurately in the least time wins.

		</DESCRIPTION>	
		<RULES>&lt;li&gt;Only one robot per team is allowed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Max no of people per team is 5.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The robots should be within 25cm * 25cm * 25cm.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Robots must be autonomous. Data links to off-board computers are allowed, but no wetware (human) operated remote controls will be permitted.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The robots must have an accessible on/off switch.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The power supply for the vehicle should be contained on-board, and should not exceed 15V between any two points in the circuit.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The time will be measured from the moment the robot crosses the starting line till it crosses the finish line. A robot is deemed to have crossed the finish line when the foremost wheel, track, or leg of the robot contacts or crosses over the line.A maximum of 3 minutes is allowed to complete the course; else this will lead to disqualification.Time shall be measured by an electronic gate system or by a judge with a stopwatch, based on the availability of equipment. In either case the recorded time shall be final.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A robot that wanders off of the arena surface will be disqualified. A robot shall be deemed to have left the arena when any wheel, leg, or track has moved completely off the arena surface.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If the robot loses the course line then it has to reacquire the line at the point at which the line was lost or an earlier traversed point. If the robot fails to do so it will be one chance to reattempt. The robot must start the course again from the beginning, and if it loses the line course on its second attempt it will be disqualified.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The decisions of all officials regarding these rules and the conduct of the event shall be final.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Robot which completes the path fully and in the best time wins.&lt;/li&gt;
</RULES>
		<TIMELINE>To be uploaded soon</TIMELINE>
		<DOWNLOADS>&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href='downloads/linefollower.pdf' target='_blank'&gt;Line Follower Details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;</DOWNLOADS>
		<CONTACTS>&lt;h4&gt;Ashish Tigga&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 8989931341&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;aashish.tigga@infotsav.org
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Divyank Shekhar Singh&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 8989931343	&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;divyankshekhar.singh@infotsav.org

                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Shishirkant Pushkar&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 8989931342&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;shishirkant.pushkar@infotsav.org

                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Anmol Rai	&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 9617044410	&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;anmol.rai@infotsav.org

                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Jagdeep Singh&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;jagdeep.singh@infotsav.org
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
													
</CONTACTS>
		<UPDATES>To be uploaded soon</UPDATES>
	</EVENT>
	<EVENT>	
		<ID>23</ID>	
		<TITLE>Open Challenge</TITLE>
		<TAGLINE></TAGLINE>
		<IMAGE>Open-Challenge.png</IMAGE>
		<DESCRIPTION>This event would be an open platform for all the budding engineers, scientists, and researchers who can come up with their innovative designs and implementations in the field of robotics and exhibit them in front of our elite panel and explain the working of their machines.
		The participants would be judged on the basis of their innovation, implementation and demonstration.The contestants are to demonstrate a robot that performs interesting tasks for applications such 
as in entertainment, domestic chores, industry etc. 

		</DESCRIPTION>	
		<RULES>&lt;li&gt;The competing robots can start from any point in the contest arena. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; A total duration of up to 10mins is allocated for setting up the robot and any accessory equipment and demonstration of its capability. The time duration will be measured from the moment the contestants enter the arena. If more than 10 minutes elapsed, the robot must be removed from the arena.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In the case where the contestants wish to employ radio control, they should inform the secretariat in advance. Contestants should not broadcast radio signals while another contestant's robot is performing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In the case that a robot requires special accessory equipment or tools during its performance,the contestants will provide such items.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In the case that a robot performance is to be accompanied by music, the contestants should provide the means to reproduce this music.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;There is no specific flooring material of the contest arena. The flooring will very much depend on the available contest site. However, if there is a special requirement such as carpet, the contestants will have to provide for it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;One power point of 220/230V, 50 Hz supply will be made available. However, the teams are to provide their own power adapter and extension means if it is required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For air supply, the contestants are to provide their own air compressor units if necessary. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The designs of the competing robots must be original and unique. No two identical designs are allowed in the competition.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The expenses incurred in transportation and setup of equipment is to be borne by the individual teams.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The boundary for the area will be black or white depending on the floor. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; Robots that can, in principle, compete in other should not be allowed to compete in the open category event.&lt;/li&gt;
</RULES>
		<TIMELINE>To be uploaded soon</TIMELINE>
		<DOWNLOADS>&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href='downloads/openchallenge.pdf' target='_blank'&gt;Open Challenge Details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;</DOWNLOADS>
		<CONTACTS>&lt;h4&gt;Ashish Tigga&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 8989931341&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;aashish.tigga@infotsav.org
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Divyank Shekhar Singh&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 8989931343	&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;divyankshekhar.singh@infotsav.org

                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Shishirkant Pushkar&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 8989931342&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;shishirkant.pushkar@infotsav.org

                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Anmol Rai	&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 9617044410	&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;anmol.rai@infotsav.org

                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Jagdeep Singh&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;jagdeep.singh@infotsav.org
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
													
</CONTACTS>
		<UPDATES>To be uploaded soon</UPDATES>
	</EVENT>
	
<EVENT>	
		<ID>24</ID>	
		<TITLE>Robo-Race</TITLE>
		<TAGLINE></TAGLINE>
		<IMAGE>Line-Sequentes.png</IMAGE>
		<DESCRIPTION>Robo Race is a simple and entry level Robotics competition where couple of Robots would be competing with each other in terms of speed and accurate control.
		There will be a race between two manually controlled robots. The robots should  be cotrolled via remote control. Each team gets only one chance and the team completing first wins the race.
		</DESCRIPTION>	
		<RULES>&lt;li&gt;Only one bot per team is allowed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Max no of people per team is 5.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Robots must be manual. Both wired and wireless remotes are allowed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Onboard power supply should be present and it should not exceed 15V between any two points.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;There is no time limit for the compltion of the race.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The robot which wanders off the arena shall be disqualified.&lt;/li&gt;

</RULES>
		<TIMELINE>To be uploaded soon</TIMELINE>
		<DOWNLOADS>&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href='downloads/roborace.pdf' target='_blank'&gt;Robo Race Details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;</DOWNLOADS>
		<CONTACTS>&lt;h4&gt;Ashish Tigga&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 8989931341&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;aashish.tigga@infotsav.org
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Divyank Shekhar Singh&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 8989931343	&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;divyankshekhar.singh@infotsav.org

                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Shishirkant Pushkar&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 8989931342&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;shishirkant.pushkar@infotsav.org

                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Anmol Rai	&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 9617044410	&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;anmol.rai@infotsav.org

                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Jagdeep Singh&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;jagdeep.singh@infotsav.org
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
													
</CONTACTS>
		<UPDATES>To be uploaded soon</UPDATES>
	</EVENT>
	<EVENT>	
		<ID>25</ID>	
		<TITLE>Robo Soccer</TITLE>
		<TAGLINE></TAGLINE>
		<IMAGE>robosoccer.png</IMAGE>
		<DESCRIPTION>Robo Soccer is a real time arcade game in which each bot is required to put a soccer ball in the desired area just like what happens in the game of football.
&lt;li&gt;Name of Event: 	        Robo Soccer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Robot per Event:		    One&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Robot Weight Range:		5 Kgs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Robot Dimensions:		    30*30*30 cms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Battery Power:			40 V {230 V}	AC/Dc&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Arena Specifications:		As per Center&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Engineering Principles:	Art, Mechanical Engineering, Electrical Engineering, Computer Science,etc.&lt;/li&gt;

		</DESCRIPTION>	
		<RULES>&lt;b&gt;Game Procedure&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Each team can have only 1 member.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Team have be pre ready with their bots .No Time will be given after the bot is on the Arena.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;There will be different colours of ball and similar posts to them. The bots have to put the balls in the respective posts.&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;b&gt;Specifications&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The dimension of the bot should not exceed 30cm x 30cm x 30cm.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The weight of the bot should not exceed 5 Kgs. (Excluding remote control and remote control wire.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In case of a wireless bot weight will be counted as (0.8x actual weight).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Readymade gear boxes, parts, chassis, control circuits and remote 
control can be used.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Bot control:&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In case of wired bots, the wires should remain slack at any instant during the fight. All the wires coming out of the machine should be stacked as a single unit. Also, the wires should be projected 1000 mm above the ground to avoid entanglement.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In case of wireless system, it should have a minimum four frequency 
remote control circuit or two dual control circuits or a transmitter receiver paired module so that the frequency interferences with opponent team can be avoided (in case of any interference in the wireless systems, they will not be considered for rematch or  in the results).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Remote controls that are readily available in the market may also be used.&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;b&gt;Battery &amp; power:&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The machine can be  powered electrically only. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Use of an IC engine in any form is not allowed. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Batteries must be sealed, immobilized electrolyte types (such as gel cells, lithium, NiCad, NiMH, or dry cells).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The electrical voltage at any point of time in the machine should not 
exceed 40 V DC/AC.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; 230V (AC) power will be provided.(wired bots).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In case of wireless bot batteries should be placed on the bot also teams 
cannot use 230V(AC) external supply.&lt;/li&gt;

</RULES>
		<TIMELINE>To be uploaded soon</TIMELINE>
		<DOWNLOADS>&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href='downloads/robosoccer.pdf' target='_blank'&gt;Robo Soccer Details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;</DOWNLOADS>
		<CONTACTS>&lt;h4&gt;Ashish Tigga&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 8989931341&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;aashish.tigga@infotsav.org
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Divyank Shekhar Singh&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 8989931343	&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;divyankshekhar.singh@infotsav.org

                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Shishirkant Pushkar&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 8989931342&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;shishirkant.pushkar@infotsav.org

                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Anmol Rai	&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 9617044410	&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;anmol.rai@infotsav.org

                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Jagdeep Singh&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;jagdeep.singh@infotsav.org
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
													
</CONTACTS>
		<UPDATES>To be uploaded soon</UPDATES>
	</EVENT>
<EVENT>	
		<ID>26</ID>	
		<TITLE>Robowars Mini</TITLE>
		<TAGLINE></TAGLINE>
		<IMAGE>Robowars-Mini.png</IMAGE>
		<DESCRIPTION>Robowars Mini is a real-time arcade game in which two opponents would be competing with their manually operated robots with the objective of immobilizing each other. 
		The last robot standing would be the winner.
&lt;li&gt;Name of Event: 	        RoboWars&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Robot per Event:		    Two&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Robot Weight Range:		4 Kgs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Robot Dimensions:		    As per Rules&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Robot Control: 	        Autonomous or Remote-control&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Arena Specifications:		As per Center&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Engineering Principles:	Art, Mechanical Engineering, Electrical Engineering, Computer Science,etc.&lt;/li&gt;

		</DESCRIPTION>	
		<RULES>&lt;li&gt;Each team can have maximum of five members.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;During the match only two team-members will participate in competition, one member will control the bot and other to guide.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Teams are allowed to switch members in different matches. &lt;/b&gt;
 
&lt;li&gt;Setup time: Team have be pre ready with their bots .No Time will be given after the bot is on the Arena.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Match duration: 5 minutes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Winning criteria: Team can either win by direct knockout  or if the time runs out and there's no knockout or both bots are inactive, the winner will be decided by the final points (Points are based on the creativity of the Bot , the team capability and the nof attacks made by the bot.)&lt;/li&gt;
 
&lt;li&gt;"A robot is declared immortal/victorious if its opponent becomes totally inactive. A robot will be declared inactive if it cannot display any movement for a time period of 30 seconds."&lt;/li&gt;
      
&lt;li&gt; The matches will be direct knock out matches ,the winners keeps on moving ahead.&lt;/li&gt; 


</RULES>
		<TIMELINE>To be uploaded soon</TIMELINE>
		<DOWNLOADS>&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href='downloads/robowars.pdf' target='_blank'&gt;Robowars Details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;</DOWNLOADS>
		<CONTACTS>&lt;h4&gt;Ashish Tigga&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 8989931341&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;aashish.tigga@infotsav.org
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Divyank Shekhar Singh&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 8989931343	&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;divyankshekhar.singh@infotsav.org

                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Shishirkant Pushkar&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 8989931342&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;shishirkant.pushkar@infotsav.org

                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Anmol Rai	&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 9617044410	&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;anmol.rai@infotsav.org

                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Jagdeep Singh&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;jagdeep.singh@infotsav.org
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
													
</CONTACTS>
		<UPDATES>To be uploaded soon</UPDATES>
	</EVENT>
	     <EVENT>	
		<ID>27</ID>	
		<TITLE>Counter Strike</TITLE>
		<TAGLINE></TAGLINE>
		<IMAGE>gamiacs.png</IMAGE>
		<DESCRIPTION>The battle of the virtual world has
		begun. Are you game? This Infotsav 12 the world will be rocked by the cyber warriors.
		Gamiacs is back with a bang. And this time it's not only more competitive and tougher
		but it has added an all new dimension in its already humungous artillery of
		entertainment.This time round different games will be organized to bring out the
		ultimate gamer who resides somewhere in you! So gear up, reload thy guns, sharpen you
		knifes and prepare for the ultimate burnout. Counter-Strike is about as close as you will ever get to saving the world; or destroying it!
		Now Counter-Strike will never be the same!
		&lt;/br&gt;
		&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Prize Money: Rs 6000 &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
		</DESCRIPTION>	
		<RULES>&lt;li&gt;Competition Method: 5 vs. 5 (Team Play, 5 players per team).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The first team to win 16 rounds is declared the winner.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In the case of a 15-15 tie after regulation:
The match go for overtime. Overtime consists of 6 rounds with starting money of $10,000. Each team will play 3 rounds as Terrorist and 3 rounds as Counter-Terrorist. The team to win 4 rounds first, is declared the winner. In the case of another tie, the overtime will be repeated until a winner is declared.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Official Maps: De_Dust2,De_Inferno,De_Nuke, De_Train &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Binding Duck to scroll wheel is not allowed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For more information, go through Downloads section&lt;/li&gt;
</RULES>
		<TIMELINE>9 Nov'12-11 Nov'12</TIMELINE>
		<DOWNLOADS>&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href='downloads/cs.pdf' target='_blank'&gt;Counter Strike Details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;</DOWNLOADS>
		<CONTACTS>&lt;h4&gt;Shubham Aggarwal&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 9098090878&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;shubham.agarwal@infotsav.org
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Rahul Sinha &lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 8989931170&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;rahul.sinha@infotsav.org
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
													
             
			 &lt;h4&gt;Shubham Taliwal&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 9425737004&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;shubham.taliwal@infotsav.org
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
	       &lt;h4&gt;Subhash Kumar&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 8989931130&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;subhash.kumar@infotsav.org
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;	
&lt;h4&gt;Mayank Shivhare&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 8889165873&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;mayank.shivhare@infotsav.org
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;														
												</CONTACTS>
		<UPDATES>To be uploaded soon</UPDATES>
	</EVENT>
	<EVENT>	
		<ID>28</ID>	
		<TITLE>NfS</TITLE>
		<TAGLINE></TAGLINE>
		<IMAGE>nfs.png</IMAGE>
		<DESCRIPTION>Hello all,There are really REALLY big prizes out there up for grabs. But they are all locked in a castle.
		All you have to do is go there get them. You can just drive 
		right through the walls at full throttle in your fully upgraded Porsche and take it all!  We are talking about 
		the much awaited Infotsav Gaming Zone which promises to be biGGer and beTTer. So be ready for Ultimate Burnout.
		&lt;/br&gt;
		&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Prize Money: Rs 1500 &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
		</DESCRIPTION>	
		<RULES>&lt;li&gt;Competition Method: 1 vs. 1 (knockout).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The use of Porsche Carrera GT and BMW M3 and Lotus Elise are not allowed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Graphic settings such as motion blur cannot be set using external utilities. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At the end of each match, players must maintain the final screens and receive confirmation from a referee.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For more information, go through Downloads section&lt;/li&gt;
</RULES>
		<TIMELINE>9 Nov'12-11 Nov'12</TIMELINE>
		<DOWNLOADS>&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href='downloads/nfs.pdf' target='_blank'&gt;Nfs Details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;</DOWNLOADS>
		<CONTACTS>&lt;h4&gt;Shubham Aggarwal&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 9098090878&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;shubham.agarwal@infotsav.org
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Rahul Sinha &lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 8989931170&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;rahul.sinha@infotsav.org
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
													
             
			 &lt;h4&gt;Shubham Taliwal&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 9425737004&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;shubham.taliwal@infotsav.org
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
	       &lt;h4&gt;Subhash Kumar&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 8989931130&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;subhash.kumar@infotsav.org
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;	
&lt;h4&gt;Mayank Shivhare&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 8889165873&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;mayank.shivhare@infotsav.org
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;</CONTACTS>
		<UPDATES>To be uploaded soon</UPDATES>
	</EVENT>
	<EVENT>	
		<ID>29</ID>	
		<TITLE>Fifa</TITLE>
		<TAGLINE></TAGLINE>
		<IMAGE>fifa.png</IMAGE>
		<DESCRIPTION>The world stands on the brink, and Makarov is intent on bringing civilization to its knees. 
		In this darkest hour you're running across an unfamiliar planet while a horde of disgusting aliens chase you. 
		You blast them with a laser and escape to safety. The adrenaline rush of driving at breakneck speeds, the pressure of
fierce competition, the fear of losing control, the intense concentration and athleticism needed to harness the power of speeding....
this is the awaited Gamiacs of Infotsav where the best in the country tackle to settle who is best in the gamble! 
This year Infotsav promises you best technology, graphics and environment for gaming.  
&lt;/br&gt;
		&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Prize Money: Rs 1500 &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
		</DESCRIPTION>	
		<RULES>&lt;li&gt;Competition Method: 1 vs. 1.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Game Mode: International and Club&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Player changes and strategy changes are limited to 3 times during the game. (The changes before the start of first and second half are not included in this count.) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the players must kick-off with a backward pass at the beginning of each half and after every goal is scored.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It is not allowed to score a goal from one's own half of the field.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For more information, go through Downloads section&lt;/li&gt;
</RULES>
		<TIMELINE>9 Nov'12-11 Nov'12</TIMELINE>
		<DOWNLOADS>&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href='downloads/fifa.pdf' target='_blank'&gt;Fifa Details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;</DOWNLOADS>
		<CONTACTS>&lt;h4&gt;Shubham Aggarwal&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 9098090878&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;shubham.agarwal@infotsav.org
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Rahul Sinha &lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 8989931170&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;rahul.sinha@infotsav.org
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
													
             
			 &lt;h4&gt;Shubham Taliwal&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 9425737004&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;shubham.taliwal@infotsav.org
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
	       &lt;h4&gt;Subhash Kumar&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 8989931130&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;subhash.kumar@infotsav.org
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;	
&lt;h4&gt;Mayank Shivhare&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 8889165873&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;mayank.shivhare@infotsav.org
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;</CONTACTS>
		<UPDATES>To be uploaded soon</UPDATES>
	</EVENT>

<EVENT>	
		<ID>30</ID>	
		<TITLE>Konferenzraum</TITLE>
		<TAGLINE>Strategy Planning</TAGLINE>
		<IMAGE>konferenzraum.png</IMAGE>
		<DESCRIPTION>You, as the future CXOs, will get a chance to live the dream as early as possible. 
		Each team should consist of 3 people where one is designated as CFO, other as COO and the last as CEO.
		As the board of a company, you have to formulate a strategy to take on business rivals and increase the business share. 
		The strategy should consist of Marketing Plan, Financial Plan and Operations Plan. There will be two rounds.
&lt;li&gt;First Prize worth   8,000/-&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Second Prize worth   4000/-&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Certificates for all Finalists present for the campus round.&lt;/li&gt;

		</DESCRIPTION>	
		<RULES> &lt;b&gt;Round 1 is an online submission round. You are required to prepare a proposal/abstract in 3 pages and mail it to the address given below before the stipulated deadline. The plan should clearly bring out the likely problems and solutions to the recommendations given by the teams. The allocation of marks for each of the strategy is as follows.&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Marketing Plan: 30% (Includes Below The Line, Advertising, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Financial Plan: 40% (Includes Restructuring, Leveraging, Equity Issue, Buy-outs, M and A, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Operations Plan: 30% (Includes Production, Outsourcing, BPR, and Supply Chain Management)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Round 2: 
Shortlisted teams from Round 1 would be invited to the ABV-IIITM, Gwalior campus for a boardroom discussion.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Rules and Regulations&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This competition is open to all students pursuing a post graduate MBA program, PGDM or equivalent, across different management institutes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Each team can comprise of a maximum of three members and should be from the same institute. There is no limit on the number of entries that can be received from a particular institute or university.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The teams need to send their entries ....@mail......with the subject line and document name as Konferenzraum_Teamname_Collegename. The body of the mail should contain the names of the team members, Course name, email Id and contact numbers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Register for the event by clicking on the link provided on the website for the same.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The proposal should be in the  pdf format.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deadline for submitting the entry is 22th October 2012, 23:59:59.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The decisions of the organizers and the panel of judges will be final and binding on all the participants.&lt;/li&gt;

</RULES>
		<TIMELINE>&lt;li&gt;Launch Date:  ____ October, 2012&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Last Date of Registration and Submission of proposal:  October, 2012&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Results:  October, 2012&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;On-campus round:  10th November, 2012&lt;/li&gt;
</TIMELINE>
		<DOWNLOADS></DOWNLOADS>
		<CONTACTS> 
		&lt;h4&gt;Namita Chakravarthy&lt;/h4&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 9907335736&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;mba_201227@iiitm.ac.in
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Nishant Pal &lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span
class="phone"&gt;Phone: &lt;/span&gt;+91 8236044925&lt;/br&gt;
                                                        &lt;span
class="phone"&gt;E-mail: &lt;/span&gt;mba_201228@iiitm.ac.in
                                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;/br&gt;
													
          </CONTACTS>
		<UPDATES>To be uploaded soon</UPDATES>
	</EVENT>
	

	
	
	
</EVENTLIST>
