<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<items>
	<item>
		<content><![CDATA[<span align="center" class="title"><font size="+4">RULES AND GUIDELINES</font></span>
<p align="justify"><font size="14">1. The competing robots can start from any point in the contest arena.<br>
2. A total duration of up to 10mins is allocated for setting up the robot and any accessory equipment and demonstration of its capability. The time duration will be measured from the moment the contestants enter the arena. If more than 10 minutes elapsed, the robot must be removed from the arena.<br>
3. In the case where the contestants wish to employ radio control, they should inform the secretariat in advance. Contestants should not broadcast radio signals while another contestant's robot is performing.<br>
4. In the case that a robot requires special accessory equipment or tools during its performance,the contestants will provide such items.<br>
5. In the case that a robot performance is to be accompanied by music, the contestants should provide the means to reproduce this music.<br>
6.There is no specific flooring material of the contest arena. The flooring will very much depend on the available contest site. However, if there is a special requirement such as carpet, the contestants will have to provide for it.<br>
7. One power point of 220/230V, 50 Hz supply will be made available. However, the teams are to provide their own power adapter and extension means if it is required.<br>
8. For air supply, the contestants are to provide their own air compressor units if necessary. <br>
9. The designs of the competing robots must be original and unique. No two identical designs are allowed in the competition.<br>
10. The expenses incurred in transportation and setup of equipment is to be borne by the individual teams.<br>
11. The boundary for the area will be black or white depending on the floor.<br>
12. Robots that can, in principle, compete in other should not be allowed to compete in the open category event.
</font></p> ]]></content>
	</item>
</items>